Guide to the Katipunan Ng Mga Demokratikong Pilipino (KDP) [Union of Democratic Filipinos] Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Katipunan ng mga Demokratikong Pilipino (KDP) [Union of Democratic Filipinos] records, 1966-1988; 5889-001; 21.54 cubic feet (24 boxes)
  - SERIES III: FILIPINO COMMUNITY LOS ANGELES, circa 1971-1987 (Box-folder 10/24-24)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Various political slide show scripts (2), circa 1976 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - "Isuda Ti Immuna" Southern California Souvenir Program; Los Angeles Mayoral Commendation for Play; Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Internal Memoranda Regarding Play, 1977 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - "Three Waves of Filipino Immigration to the United States" speech: Vince Reyes, circa 1976 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - "Isuda Ti Immuna" (They Who Came First) Script, 1977 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Southern California Regional Headquarters Plans, Notes, 1977 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Southern California Regional Congress: Reports, Notes, circa 1976 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) San Diego Chapter Plans, Strategy, 1980 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Los Angeles Chapter Plans, San Diego Chapter Plans, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) One Year National Plans, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) One Year Plans: National and Southern California Regional, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Northern California Regional Congress, 1979 (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) East Coast Regional Congress, circa 1977 (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Ang Katipunan Workshop: News writing Workshop, Undated (Box-folder 12/15)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Cultural Workshop, 1977 (Box-folder 12/16)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Propagand Workshop, circa 1977 (Box-folder 12/17)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Childcare plans, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 12/18)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Various funding proposals, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 12/19)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Various internal communiques, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 12/20)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Various finance-related documents, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 12/21)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Response to Police Surveillance: Los Angeles, 1978 (Box-folder 12/22)
    - Legal exhibits from Tom Gerard and Roy Bullock Spying Case, circa 1993 (Box-folder 12/23)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Political Lines for 1979 Pilipino People's Far West Convention, 1978 (Box-folder 12/24)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) 10th Anniversary Celebration Mobilization, 1983 (Box-folder 12/25)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) National Theoretical School, 1980 (Box-folder 12/26)
    - Organizing Committee for an Ideological Center (OCIC) Minority Conference and National Network of Marxist-Leninist Clubs (NNMLC) Response, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 12/27)
    - National Network of Marxist-Leninist Clubs (NNMLC), 1980 (Box-folder 12/28)
    - Marxist-Leninist Organizational Study, 1980 (Box-folder 12/29)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) "On Practice" Study Guides, 1975 (Box-folder 12/30)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Tactical Study Guide; "Oppose Individualism! Combat Liberalism!", circa 1975 (Box-folder 12/31)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) "On Contradiction" Study Guide, 1975 (Box-folder 12/32)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Internal Guidelines for the 10th Anniversary of the New People's Army, 1979 (Box-folder 12/33)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) "On the Relation of the Sexes" Study, circa 1975 (Box-folder 12/34)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Guidelines for National Democratic Curriculm, 1977 (Box-folder 12/35)
    - Human Rights and the Anti-Imperialist Movement in the United States, circa 1978 (Box-folder 12/36)
    - Katipunan ng mga Demokratikong Pilipino (KDP) Union of Democratic Filipinos 1st National Congress, 1973 (Box-folder 12/37)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Hawaii Chapter Plan, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 12/38)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Ang Aktibista (The Activist) Theoretical Bulletin of the KDP, 1973-1984 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Southern California 5th Regional Congress, 1981 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) 2nd National Congress, 1975 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Union of Democratic Filiipinos (KDP) Awit ng Pakikibaka (Songs of Struggle) Songbook, circa 1975 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Dare to Struggle, Dare to Win!, Poems and Essays from the Philippine Struggle, circa 1975 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - The Philippines: Makibaka, huwag matakot! Struggle, don't be afraid., circa 1971 (Box-folder 13/6)
    - File 9: The Press Reports on the Marcos Dictatorship, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - File 10: Cultural Activism and the KDP's (Union of Democratic Filipinos) Sining Bayan, Memoirs, Historical and Critical Articles, 1999 (Box-folder 13/8)
    - File 11: Various Filipino-issues pamphlets, brochures, leaflets, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 13/9)
    - File 12: Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Tala-arawang Bayan, People's Calendar, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13/10)
    - File 13: Sourcebook on Philippine Women in Struggle, 1985 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - File 14: The United Front in the Philippines: Preparing for Revolution, 1978 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: Andres Bonifacio Day, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 13/13-16)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: Sacramento, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: Asian Americans for Jesse Jackson, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 13/18)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: COPAO San Diego, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: KDP - Weber Forum, 1979 (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: Affirmative Action, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 13/21)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: NABE 85 14th Annual Conference, 1985 (Box-folder 13/22)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: Oakland Bilingual Education, 1985 (Box-folder 13/23)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: Anti-Bakke Work, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 13/24)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: KDP - Bakke Forum, 1977 (Box-folder 13/25)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: Bakke Case Newspaper Articles, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 13/26-27)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files: Bakke Case, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 13/28)
    - Box 14: Union of Democratic Filipinos Political Campaign Files, Undated (Box-folder 14)
    - Box 15: Union of Democratic Filipinos: Various Political Slide show scripts and slides, Undated (Box-folder 15)
    - Box 16: Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP): Ang Katipunan Newspaper Story Files, Undated (Box-folder 16)
    - Box 17: Various Political slide shows, Undated (Box-folder 17)
    - Box 18: Various political issues, campaign slides, Undated (Box-folder 18)
    - Box 19: Various political issues, campaign slides, Undated (Box-folder 19)
    - Box 20: Various political slide shows and scripts, Undated (Box-folder 20)
    - Box 21: Union of Democratic Filipinos: Ang Katipunan Newspaper Story Files, Undated (Box-folder 21)
    - Box 22: Various political issues, campaign slides, Undated (Box-folder 22)
    - Box 23: Video tape and audio reels, Undated (Box-folder 23)
    - Box 24: Political Prisoner Support T-shirts, Committee to Advance the Movement for Democracy and Independence (CAMDI) Banner, Undated (Box-folder 24)